<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>HTML Codex</title>
	<atom:link href="https://htmlcodex.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://htmlcodex.com/</link>
	<description>Free HTML Templates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:58:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://i0.wp.com/htmlcodex.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/cropped-favicon-2.png?fit=32%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url>
	<title>HTML Codex</title>
	<link>https://htmlcodex.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">168936011</site>	<item>
		<title>SEOcom &#8211; SEO Company Website Template</title>
		<link>https://htmlcodex.com/seo-company-website-template/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anamul Hasan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IT firm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[seo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[seo agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web designer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://htmlcodex.com/?p=3811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEOcom is a modern, clean, and fully responsive SEO company website template designed for SEO agencies, digital marketing firms, and online marketing professionals. Built with performance and usability in mind, SEOcom helps you create a strong, professional online presence that converts visitors into clients. This SEO agency website template is available in two flexible versions: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/seo-company-website-template/">SEOcom &#8211; SEO Company Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>SEOcom is a modern, clean, and fully responsive SEO company website template designed for SEO agencies, digital marketing firms, and online marketing professionals. Built with performance and usability in mind, SEOcom helps you create a strong, professional online presence that converts visitors into clients.</p>



<p>This SEO agency website template is available in two flexible versions: Free and Pro, making it suitable for both beginners and professional agencies.</p>



<p>The Free version of SEOcom includes the essential pages needed to launch a basic SEO website. It comes with a well-structured Home, About, Services, and Contact page, making it ideal for startups, freelancers, or small SEO businesses looking for a simple and effective solution.</p>



<p>The Pro version of this SEO company HTML template offers a complete and advanced website solution with 13+ professionally designed demo pages. These include Home, About, Services, Service Detail, Projects, Project Detail, FAQs, Pricing, Features, Team, Testimonials, 404 Error Page, and Contact Page. Each page is carefully crafted to showcase services, highlight expertise, and build trust with potential clients.</p>



<p>SEOcom Pro also includes a fully functional Ajax and PHP contact form, ensuring fast, secure, and reliable communication with clients. This advanced contact form functionality is available only in the Pro version.</p>



<p>Designed using clean HTML5 and CSS3, SEOcom adheres to modern UI/UX standards and offers a fast-loading, SEO-optimized structure. Its responsive layout ensures flawless performance across all devices, helping improve user experience and search engine visibility. As a powerful SEO agency HTML template, SEOcom is optimized to support higher rankings and better online performance.</p>



<p>Whether you choose the Free or Pro version, SEOcom provides a solid foundation for building a professional and results-driven SEO agency website.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Key Features</h4>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Bootstrap v5 Framework</li>



<li>Font Awesome 5 Free Icons</li>



<li>Fully Responsive Design</li>



<li>Clean &amp; SEO-Friendly Code</li>



<li>Cross-Browser Compatibility</li>



<li>13+ HTML demo pages (Pro Only)</li>



<li>Ajax &amp; PHP Contact Form (Pro Only)</li>



<li>Full Documentation (Pro Only)</li>



<li>Well-Organized Files</li>



<li>Easy Customization</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/seo-company-website-template/">SEOcom &#8211; SEO Company Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3811</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Charitize &#8211; Charity Organization Website Template</title>
		<link>https://htmlcodex.com/charity-organization-website-template/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[HTML Codex]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Nonprofit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[charity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[funding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fundraising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non profit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nonprofit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://htmlcodex.com/?p=3641</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Charitize is a free charity organization website template that is a simple, responsive, and professionally designed one or multi-page template built on Bootstrap v5. It’s tailored specifically for nonprofit organizations, NGOs, charity foundations, community groups, donation and fundraising initiatives that want a polished web presence without the complexity of a heavy CMS. If you&#8217;re looking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/charity-organization-website-template/">Charitize &#8211; Charity Organization Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Charitize is a free charity organization website template that is a simple, responsive, and professionally designed one or multi-page template built on Bootstrap v5. It’s tailored specifically for nonprofit organizations, NGOs, charity foundations, community groups, donation and fundraising initiatives that want a polished web presence without the complexity of a heavy CMS.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re looking for free <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/template/nonprofit/">nonprofit website templates</a>, then you&#8217;re in the right place. Charitize is ideal for organizations of all sizes: from small local charities to medium-sized foundations looking for a solid starter website. This free HTML template includes well-structured HTML, CSS, and JavaScript assets, and examples of common content patterns (donation forms, event section, volunteer signup, donation cases, team section, testimonial, and call-to-action).</p>



<p>One of the strongest advantages of this free non profit organization website template is its simplicity. Because it is built with Bootstrap v5 and clean semantic HTML, even users with basic web development knowledge can get started quickly. You can easily replace demo text, update colors, and swap images without needing to modify complex code. Developers who need deeper customization can extend it with Bootstrap utilities or their own CSS. At the same time, beginners can launch a functional charity website by editing just a few lines of HTML.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Free Charity Organization Website Template</h4>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>HTML5 and CSS3</li>



<li>Bootstrap v5</li>



<li>Sass supported</li>



<li>Google font support</li>



<li>Bootstrap icon support</li>



<li>Font Awesome icon font</li>



<li>10+ pre-built demo pages</li>



<li>Well-commented code</li>



<li>Developer-friendly code</li>



<li>Responsive design</li>



<li>Browsers compatibility</li>



<li>Sticky top navbar</li>



<li>Dropdown navbar</li>



<li>Header carousel</li>



<li>Animated play button</li>



<li>Popup YouTube video</li>



<li>Smooth scrolling</li>



<li>Progress bar</li>



<li>Number counter</li>



<li>Event section</li>



<li>Donation form</li>



<li>Call-to-action</li>



<li>Testimonial carousel</li>



<li>CSS3 hover effects</li>



<li>Newsletter form</li>



<li>Social link with icon</li>



<li>“Back to Top” button</li>



<li>Contact form</li>



<li>Google map</li>



<li>Easy to use</li>
</ul>



<p>This free charity organization website template, built with Bootstrap v5, is more than just a starting point. This free template is a complete and adaptable solution for charity and nonprofit organizations to create a professional and impactful website. Download for free, create, and publish your website.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/charity-organization-website-template/">Charitize &#8211; Charity Organization Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3641</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Poseify &#8211; Modeling Agency Website Template</title>
		<link>https://htmlcodex.com/modeling-agency-website-template/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[HTML Codex]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[creative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[creative agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fashion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modeling agency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://htmlcodex.com/?p=3631</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Poseify is a sleek, professional, and free modeling agency website template built with Bootstrap v5, tailored for agencies, talent managers, and modeling professionals. It combines a modern, image-focused design with the flexibility and reliability of the Bootstrap framework, making it perfect for agencies seeking a professional online presence without the overhead of a custom build. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/modeling-agency-website-template/">Poseify &#8211; Modeling Agency Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Poseify is a sleek, professional, and free modeling agency website template built with Bootstrap v5, tailored for agencies, talent managers, and modeling professionals. It combines a modern, image-focused design with the flexibility and reliability of the Bootstrap framework, making it perfect for agencies seeking a professional online presence without the overhead of a custom build.</p>



<p>This free model agency website template is perfect for agencies of all sizes, from boutique firms launching their first digital presence to well-established agencies upgrading their portfolio showcase. Whether your agency focuses on fashion, commercial, fitness, or influencer marketing, Poseify provides a versatile foundation that grows with your brand. Poseify emphasizes fast loading, SEO optimization, and clean, accessible design, ensuring your website looks and performs flawlessly.</p>



<p>Poseify&#8217;s clean, well-decorated, and commented codebase allows seamless customization. Developers can easily modify color schemes using Bootstrap variables, swap out typography with Google Fonts, integrate headless CMS platforms for dynamic content, and add custom animations or scripts without breaking the layout. Whether you&#8217;re looking to build a static business website or integrate with platforms like WordPress, this free model agency HTML template provides a robust foundation for scalability.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Free Modeling Agency Website Template</h4>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap v5</li>



<li>FontAwesome and Bootstrap icons</li>



<li>Free Google web fonts integrated</li>



<li>Editable colors, fonts, and layouts</li>



<li>Fully responsive design</li>



<li>SEO-friendly structure</li>



<li>8+ fast-loading demo pages</li>



<li>Sticky and mobile-friendly navbar</li>



<li>Elegant header carousel</li>



<li>Portfolio showcase sections</li>



<li>Popup image gallery</li>



<li>Scrolling and animation effects</li>



<li>Testimonials carousel</li>



<li>Social media integration</li>



<li>Newsletter and contact form</li>



<li>Cross-browser compatibility</li>



<li>Animated footer background</li>



<li>Google Maps integration</li>



<li>CSS hover effects</li>



<li>Casting form</li>



<li>Call-to-action</li>



<li>Free to download</li>



<li>Easy to use</li>
</ul>



<p>Download Poseify, a free and responsive modeling agency website template built with Bootstrap 5. Perfect for talent portfolios, casting agencies, and fashion modeling. Easy to customize, SEO-optimized, and mobile-friendly for a stunning online presence.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/modeling-agency-website-template/">Poseify &#8211; Modeling Agency Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3631</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plasery &#8211; Plastic Surgery Website Template</title>
		<link>https://htmlcodex.com/plastic-surgery-website-template/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[HTML Codex]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Medical & Hospital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[clinic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cosmetic surgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doctor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hospital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[plastic surgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[skin & beauty care]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[surgeon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://htmlcodex.com/?p=3621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Plasery &#8211; free plastic surgery website template is a modern, professional, and fully responsive HTML design tailored specifically for cosmetic surgeons, clinics, hospitals, doctors, medical centers, skin care centers, and beauty professionals offering aesthetic procedures. Built with clean HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap v5, this free template delivers an elegant yet responsive layout that captures attention [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/plastic-surgery-website-template/">Plasery &#8211; Plastic Surgery Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Plasery &#8211; free plastic surgery website template is a modern, professional, and fully responsive HTML design tailored specifically for cosmetic surgeons, clinics, hospitals, doctors, medical centers, skin care centers, and beauty professionals offering aesthetic procedures. Built with clean HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap v5, this free template delivers an elegant yet responsive layout that captures attention from the very first glance.</p>



<p>Since more than half of web visitors today browse on mobile devices, this free cosmetic surgery website template is fully responsive, meaning your website will look and function perfectly on smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktops. Fully responsive layout of the template ensures that every part of the website is easy to use on touch screens, images resize gracefully, and no content is lost regardless of the device used. This focus on accessibility not only enhances user experience but also boosts your site’s SEO performance, helping your business rank higher in search engines.</p>



<p>Every business has its own personality, branding, and target audience. Your website should reflect that uniqueness. This is why our free skin surgery website template is designed to be highly customizable. Built on the Bootstrap 5 framework, it offers flexibility for you to modify colors, typography, layouts, and content sections without requiring advanced programming knowledge. Whether you prefer a minimalist style with ample white space or a more vibrant, image-heavy approach, this free template is adaptable to your needs.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Free Plastic Surgery Website Template</h4>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap v5</li>



<li>FontAwesome and Bootstrap icons</li>



<li>Free Google web fonts integrated</li>



<li>Editable colors, fonts, and layouts</li>



<li>Fully responsive design</li>



<li>SEO-friendly structure</li>



<li>9+ fast-loading demo pages</li>



<li>Elegant hero header</li>



<li>Service showcase sections</li>



<li>Popup video and play button</li>



<li>Fact number counter</li>



<li>Before-and-after image</li>



<li>Appointment booking form</li>



<li>Scrolling and animation effects</li>



<li>Testimonials carousel</li>



<li>Social media integration</li>



<li>Newsletter and contact form</li>



<li>Google Maps integration</li>



<li>Cross-browser compatibility</li>



<li>Call-to-action</li>



<li>Free to download</li>



<li>Easy to use</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/plastic-surgery-website-template/">Plasery &#8211; Plastic Surgery Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3621</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Electro &#8211; Electronics Website Template</title>
		<link>https://htmlcodex.com/electronics-website-template/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[HTML Codex]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[eCommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e-commerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electrical shop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electronics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[store]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://htmlcodex.com/?p=3609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Electro is a free electronics website template built with HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap 5 framework, meticulously crafted for ecommerce entrepreneurs, startups, resellers, and electronic retailers who want to build a solid online storefront without incurring upfront development costs. Fully customizable, scalable, and packed with powerful website design elements, this free Bootstrap shop template empowers users [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/electronics-website-template/">Electro &#8211; Electronics Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Electro is a free electronics website template built with HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap 5 framework, meticulously crafted for ecommerce entrepreneurs, startups, resellers, and electronic retailers who want to build a solid online storefront without incurring upfront development costs. Fully customizable, scalable, and packed with powerful website design elements, this free <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/bootstrap-shop-template/">Bootstrap shop template</a> empowers users to launch a full-fledged electronics store with ease.</p>



<p>In the modern world where digital transformation drives the global economy, e-commerce has emerged as the most powerful channel for retail success. From smartphones and laptops to smartwatches, gaming consoles, and accessories, electronics are among the most popular products sold online. As a result, having an intuitive, fast, mobile-friendly, and feature-rich website is no longer optional, but it&#8217;s the foundation of digital retail success.</p>



<p>The free electronics <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/template/ecommerce/">ecommerce website template</a> is created to solve a fundamental challenge for electronics businesses: going digital quickly, affordably, and professionally. It provides an out-of-the-box solution that allows anyone, developers and non-developers, to create an elegant, responsive, and high-performing website to sell gadgets, accessories, or parts. It works flawlessly across iOS and Android phones, iPads and tablets, desktop browsers, and large 4K screens.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Free Electronics Website Template Features</h4>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>HTML5 and CSS3</li>



<li>Bootstrap 5</li>



<li>Clean code</li>



<li>Bootstrap Icons</li>



<li>FontAwesome Icons</li>



<li>Browser compatibility</li>



<li>Google fonts</li>



<li>Sass coding</li>



<li>Fully responsive</li>



<li>8+ demo pages</li>



<li>Header carousel</li>



<li>Search form</li>



<li>Product filter</li>



<li>Cart system</li>



<li>Accordion</li>



<li>Product carousel</li>



<li>Ratings &amp; reviews</li>



<li>Blog system</li>



<li>Newsletter form</li>



<li>Contact form</li>



<li>Google map</li>



<li>Testimonials carousel</li>



<li>Free to use and modify</li>
</ul>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re selling phones, tablets, CPUs, chargers, Bluetooth devices, or any consumer tech, this free electronic shop website template provides the essential tools to go online fast without compromising quality, professionalism, or user experience. If you&#8217;re serious about launching or scaling your electronics e-commerce venture, this free electronics website template is your perfect launchpad. Download, customize, and go live within hours, not weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/electronics-website-template/">Electro &#8211; Electronics Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3609</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salone &#8211; Beauty Salon Website Template</title>
		<link>https://htmlcodex.com/beauty-salon-website-template/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[HTML Codex]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 07:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Beauty & Hair]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[beauty salon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[beauty shop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hair salon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[haircare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[haircut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[parlour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[skin & beauty care]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spa center]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://htmlcodex.com/?p=3597</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Salone &#8211; free beauty salon website template is crafted to suit a wide range of beauty-related businesses, including hair salons, beauty parlours, spas, nail bars, makeup artists, skin care clinics, massage therapy centers, eyelash &#38; brow studios, and other beauty professionals. A well-designed website acts as a digital gateway, attracting potential clients, showcasing services, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/beauty-salon-website-template/">Salone &#8211; Beauty Salon Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Salone &#8211; free beauty salon website template is crafted to suit a wide range of beauty-related businesses, including hair salons, beauty parlours, spas, nail bars, makeup artists, skin care clinics, massage therapy centers, eyelash &amp; brow studios, and other beauty professionals.</p>



<p>A well-designed website acts as a digital gateway, attracting potential clients, showcasing services, and solidifying the brand&#8217;s reputation. Salone &#8211; free beauty salon HTML template, a fully responsive, elegant, and user-friendly web tool, empowers you to establish a professional and captivating web presence.</p>



<p>This free <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/hair-salon-html-template/">hair salon website template</a> is a sleek, clean, and modern design built from the ground up using industry-standard technologies like HTML5, CSS3, and the Bootstrap 5 framework. Designed with responsiveness and usability in mind, it adapts flawlessly to desktops, tablets, and mobile devices, ensuring that your website looks great no matter what device your customers are using.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Beauty Salon Website Template Features</h4>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Valid HTML5 and CSS3</li>



<li>Bootstrap v5 framework</li>



<li>Sass supported coding</li>



<li>Responsive layout</li>



<li>Customizable 10+ demo pages</li>



<li>Smooth navigation</li>



<li>Header carousel</li>



<li>Services showcase</li>



<li>Popup photo gallery</li>



<li>Pricing table</li>



<li>Testimonials slider</li>



<li>Contact form,</li>



<li>Blog section</li>



<li>Social media links</li>



<li>Newsletter form</li>



<li>Cross-browser compatibility</li>



<li>SEO optimized markup</li>



<li>Font Awesome Icons</li>



<li>Bootstrap icons</li>



<li>Google fonts integration</li>



<li>Free to use and modify</li>
</ul>



<p>Salone &#8211; <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/spa-html-template">free beauty parlour HTML website template</a> is not just a starting point &#8211; it’s a canvas for your brand’s digital expression. With thoughtful UX design, graceful CSS animations, and clean code, it reflects the calm, care, and class of a professional salon experience. Whether you want a single landing page or an expanded multi-page site, this free hair salon web template can scale with your vision. It&#8217;s more than a design; it&#8217;s an opportunity to make a lasting impression. And best of all &#8211; it&#8217;s free, fully customizable, and ready to elevate your beauty salon business to new heights online.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://htmlcodex.com/beauty-salon-website-template/">Salone &#8211; Beauty Salon Website Template</a> appeared first on <a href="https://htmlcodex.com">HTML Codex</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3597</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/?utm_source=w3tc&utm_medium=footer_comment&utm_campaign=free_plugin

Page Caching using Disk: Enhanced 

Served from: htmlcodex.com @ 2026-01-30 09:43:29 by W3 Total Cache
-->
Ask
Explain this
Select
Please explain in ${lang}: "${selection}"
RMH6BQATO7S4NKOI
Paste selection

AITOPIA
Submit (enter)
Make a Review & Earn Credit ❤
Chat
Ask
Search
Write
Image
ChatFile
Vision
Agent
Full Page
Invite & Earn
